site2corp.com 2016-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Site2Corp

This Privacy Policy explains what kind of your Information will be Collected by Site2Corp when you use Site2Corp.com (the "site") and related services (the "Service") 

**Cookies Information**

When you visit Site2Corp.com, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. Site2Corp uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Log File Information: Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you register with or view our site, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

**How we use your Information**

We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service. Site2Corp never discloses your personal information to any third party unless you have instructed us to do so. 

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service (for instance, in User Content you post) becomes available to the public via the Service and our business partners. User Content includes, but is not limited to, reviews, quotes, authors and comments. If you remove your content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored the content posted by you. 

By providing Site2Corp your email address you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters and promotional mails, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by clicking the unsubscribe link present in the footer of mails. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers. You may not opt out of Service-related e-mails. 

We may share Collected Information with certain of our third party service providers (e.g., our web hosting provider whose server logs collect the non-personal information in order to provide the Site to you. We may also share Collected Information with some of our business and marketing partners in furthering our mission as an organization or delivering the content, materials, and services available on or through the Site to you. Specifically, though, we may share your personal information with the following third party service providers: 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the Site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

comScore, Inc as a third party vendor, uses cookies to identify and collect anonymous user interests on the Site via its Scorecard Research program. You may opt out of this cookie by visiting the Scorecard Research Preference Manager. 

If all or part of our company is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity, we may transfer Collected Information to such entity as part of that transaction. 

Site2Corp may use certain information about you and/or your User Content without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how the Service is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing advertisements and promotions. 

Site2Corp reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor the Content you post on the site. We have the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason, including without limitation, if in its sole opinion, such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Use Agreement or to protect or defend its rights or property or those of any third party. Site2Corp also reserves the right to remove information upon the request of any third party for voilating copyright or for any other reasons. 

We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in. 

**Links to Other Websites**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including those that have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our website to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us by writing a mail to support@Site2Corp.com
